(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
宝鐘マリン100万人記念ライブ Connected Fantasia
Houshou Marine 1 Million Subscribers Anniversary Live Connected Fantasia
MARINE CH. PRESENTS
3D SPECIAL LIVE
Marine Ch. 宝鐘マリン チャンネル登録者数 1,000,000人
Marine Ch. Houshou Marine - Subscriber Count: 1,000,000
宝鐘マリン HOUSHOU MARINE
Houshou Marine
兎田ぺこら USADA PEKORA
Usada Pekora
潤羽るしあ URUHA RUSHIA
Uruha Rushia
不知火フレア SHIRANUI FLARE
Shiranui Flare
白銀ノエル SHIROGANE NOEL
Shirogane Noel
Connected Fantasia
キミたち！100万人、ありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you for 1 million subscribers!
それでは今日も一日、適当に合いの手入れてってくださーい！
Now then, please enjoy the day and join in with the cheers!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Lost my music 宝鐘マリン
Lost my music - Houshou Marine
星空見上げ 私だけの
Looking up at the starry sky,
光を教えて
Show me my own light.
あなたは今どこで誰と
Where are you now, and who are you with?
いるのでしょう
I wonder...
楽しくしてると思うと
Thinking that you're having fun
寂しくなって
Makes me feel lonely.
一緒に見たシネマ
The movie we watched together,
一人きりで鳴らす
I play it all alone.
大好きな人が遠い
The person I love is far,
遠すぎて泣きたくなるの
So far away that I want to cry.
明日目が覚めたら ほら
When I wake up tomorrow, look,
希望が生まれるかも Good night
Hope might be born. Good night.
I still I still I love you
I'm waiting waiting forever
止まらないのよ ハイ！
It won't stop, Go!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Go! Go! Go! Go!
眠りの淵で夢がくれる
At the edge of sleep, a dream gives me
思い出のワンデー
A day of memories.
あなたの言葉には少し
In your words,
嘘があった
There was a little lie.
離さないよと君だけだと
Saying you'd never let go, and only me,
抱きしめたのに
Even though you hugged me.
約束がふわりと暗い
The promise vanished softly
夜に消えた
Into the dark night.
大好きな人よいつも
My beloved, I'll always,
いつまでも探してしまう
Forever be searching for you.
きっと目が覚めてもまだ
Even if I wake up, I'll surely still
幻を感じた今に
Be in this moment where I felt a phantom.
I lost I lost I lost you
You're making making my music
もう逢えないのよ No!
I can't see you anymore. No!
大好きな人が遠い
The person I love is far,
遠すぎて泣きたくなるの
So far away that I want to cry.
明日目が覚めたら ほら
When I wake up tomorrow, look,
希望が生まれるかも Good night
Hope might be born. Good night.
切ないひとときが 遠い遠すぎて泣きたくなるの
A painful moment is too far, too far, and it makes me want to cry
日が醒めてもまだ幻を感じたいもんに
Even after waking up, I still want to feel the phantom
I wish I wish I love you, I'm waiting waiting forever
I wish I wish I love you, たまらないのよ
I wish I wish I love you, I can't stand it
I wish I wish I love you, I'm waiting waiting forever
I wish I wish I love you, また会えるよね ね！
I wish I wish I love you, we can meet again, right? Right!
はーい！ いや、もう…なんですかね？
Hi! Wow, well... what can I say?
もうすごいね、調整に調整を重ねてついにこの100万人記念ライブが
It's amazing. After repeated adjustments, finally, this 1-million subscriber anniversary live...
来ました！
...is here!
今日は、まあサムネイルとか色々見て、お察しの通りですね
Today, as you might have guessed from the thumbnail and everything...
なんと3期生のみんなとちょっと歌っていこうかなと思ってまして
...I'm planning to sing a bit with all the 3rd generation members.
ちょっとね、どんな感じのライブなのかは、まあ見てのお楽しみということで
Well, you'll have to watch and see what kind of live it is.
ちょっと最後までね、色々とこだわって詰め込みましたので、選曲とかね
I've put a lot of effort into everything until the end, including the song choices...
そのいろんなところ、船長もいろいろ考えたので、ちょっと船長のやりたいを詰め込ませてもらった
...and various other things. I thought about a lot, so I've packed in everything I wanted to do...
ライブとなってますので、ちょっと3期生がね登場もお楽しみにしていてください
...into this live. So please look forward to the appearances of the 3rd generation members.
それじゃあまずは誰が来るのかな？
Now then, who's coming first?
あ、そうだ。ちょっと今日はね、ハッシュタグ…何だったっけ？ ハッシュタグ…
Oh, that's right. For today... what was the hashtag again? Hashtag...
宝鐘マリン100万人記念…
Houshou Marine 1-million anniversary...
宝鐘マリン100万人記念でいっぱい呟いてください
Please tweet a lot with #HoushouMarine1MillionAnniversary.
スクショとかもねしてくださいね。イェーイ。可愛いところいっぱいお見せするんでスクショよろしく！
Take screenshots too! Yay. I'll show you many cute moments, so please take screenshots!
ということで、じゃあ最初のゲストは誰かな？
So, who's the first guest?
というわけで、じゃあ早速、次のステージへ！ 出航！
Alright, let's head to the next stage right away! Setting sail!
シャカビーチ〜Laka Laka La〜
白銀ノエル・宝鐘マリン
Shaka Beach ~Laka Laka La~
Shirogane Noel & Houshou Marine
ギラギラのビーチウェー
Glistening beach-way
夏のほうアゲイン
Summer's back again
願って身勝手な人世のゲーム
Wishing for a selfish game of life
ロックオン 君を待ってたんだ バッド、ワイド、オン、ユー
Lock-on, I was waiting for you. Bad, wide, on you
ギラギラの瞳で
With glistening eyes
不徳プレイとチューン
Immoral play and tune
横切ったビキニ ガン見のスコープ
Bikinis passing by, staring through the scope
ロックオン 1人だけ
Lock-on, only one person
ロックオン 苦渋の選択
Lock-on, a difficult choice
逆らってでもこの 刺激に満ちた季節を
Even if I defy it, this season full of stimulation...
終わらせない
...I won't let it end.
夏が今 僕の心
Summer is now spreading my heart...
広げてく
...wide.
波風 笑い声
Sea breeze, laughter
Laka Laka Love Laka Laka Love
この空 雲 虹
This sky, clouds, rainbow
にのっかって
...riding on them
砂浜の君の足跡
Your footprints on the sandy beach
見つけ出すから
I'll find them
Laka Laka Love Laka Laka Love
夜は群がって ビーチ向かいのバー
Flocking at night to the bar across the beach
今宵も探すで 愛のゲーム
Searching again tonight for the game of love
俺が司令塔 そして特攻切る
I'm the command tower, and I'll break through
お前はアシストパス出す。オーケー？
You give the assist pass. Okay?
行こうか 夜の同志達よ
Shall we go, comrades of the night?
企みだらけの ただれた関係
A festering relationship full of schemes
ロックオン 当たっても砕けるな
Lock-on, don't break even if you hit
ロックオン 栗染めの月影
Lock-on, chestnut-dyed moonlight
惑わされ 地上なんかより先に鼓動
Deluded, the heartbeat ahead of the ground...
近づく唇が 解き放つハバネロ言語
Lips approaching release Habanero language
それも悪くない
That's not bad either
夏が今 僕の心
Summer is now spreading my heart...
広げてく
...wide.
波風 笑い声
Sea breeze, laughter
Laka Laka Love Laka Laka Love
この空 雲 虹
This sky, clouds, rainbow
にのっかって
...riding on them
高台 見下ろして
Looking down from the heights
耳澄ましたら
If you listen closely
Laka Laka Love Laka Laka Love
Lonely Lonely Lonely Lonely
愛にギラギラ連れてきたけど
I brought glistening to love, but...
Lonely Lonely Lonely Lonely
心の中は No
Inside my heart is... No
まどろむ 答えは波のシラベ
Drowsing, the answer is the melody of the waves
探す足跡 消えてゆく前に
Searching for footprints before they disappear
君の 光の色が 広がってく
The color of your light is spreading
海風 笑い声が ラカラカラ ラカラカラ
Sea breeze, the sound of laughter, ra-ka-ra-ka-ra...
この 空 雲 道に のっかって
Riding on this sky, clouds, and road
砂浜の 君の足跡 見つけたから
Because I found your footprints on the beach
夏が 今 君と僕を 引き寄せる
Summer is now pulling you and me together
沈まない太陽 ラカラカラ ラカラカラ
The sun that never sets, ra-ka-ra-ka-ra...
もう 春も 秋も 冬も 跳び越してゆけ
Leap across spring, autumn, and winter
まだ夏を 終わらせない この夏は
I won't let summer end yet, this summer...
ア ラカラカラ ラカラカラ
Ah, ra-ka-ra-ka-ra, ra-ka-ra-ka-ra
はーい！ノエルー！フゥー！
Hi! Noel! Whew!
すごーい！イエーイ！
Amazing! Yay!
はい、というわけで、最初の曲は、ノエルが来てくれましたー！
Alright, so for the first song, Noel came to join me!
はーい！マリンおめでとう！
Yes! Congratulations, Marine!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ノエルとはね、まあお察しの通りのこの格好。白銀組。
With Noel, well, as you can guess from these outfits. Shirogane-gumi.
そうです。サングラスもしちゃったりして。おしゃれでしょ。
That's right. Even wearing sunglasses. Stylish, right?
いやもうね、船長はこのノエルの、なんて言ったらいいの、この前衛的なラップにね...
I mean, Senchou was, how should I say, at this Noel's avant-garde rap...
前衛的なラップ！
Avant-garde rap!
いやなんか最初はね、聞くたびにね、笑ってしまってね、膝からこうやって崩れ落ち続けて...
Well, at first, every time I heard it, I'd laugh and just keep collapsing on my knees like this...
膝から崩れ落ちてたんだけど、さすがに何回も...
I was collapsing on my knees, but after several times...
そうだね。
True.
聞いたら、ちょっと、だいぶね、耐性がついたというか。様になってたね、イエーイ！
After listening, I've developed quite a bit of resistance, or rather... it was looking good, yeah!
ちょっと威圧感が出てたかなと思います。どうだった、ノエちゃん、一緒に歌って。
I think it had a bit of an intimidating vibe. How was it, Noe-chan, singing together?
いやー、でもやっぱさ、一人で歌うのと全然違うなと思って。
Well, it's really different from singing alone.
いやでも、マリンなんか、すげーかっこよかったなと思って。
But I thought Marine was really cool.
あ、本当？ 本当。すごい。
Oh, really? Really. Amazing.
いや、この曲絶対一人だったらきついけど、なんかノエルにきついところ全部投げたんで。
Well, this song would definitely be tough alone, but I threw all the hard parts at Noel.
サビの高いところ全部ノエルに。
All the high parts in the chorus to Noel.
投げすぎー！うまー！楽しかったねー！
You threw too many! So good! That was fun!
楽しかったー！
It was fun!
いやー、ノエル、まだまだね、この後もね、続いていくわけですけども。
Well, Noel, it's going to continue after this.
お、続くのか。イエーイ。
Oh, it's continuing? Yay.
次のね、ゲストね、誰だと思う？
Who do you think the next guest is?
えー、でも、どうだろうな。るしあ？
Hmm, I wonder. Rushia?
るーちゃんももちろん来るけど、え、じゃあ、ぺこらっちょかな？
Ru-chan will obviously come too, but maybe Pekoratcho?
ぺこらっちょももちろん来るけどね、次はね、フレアが来るんだ。
Pekoratcho is coming too, of course, but next is Flare.
おー、フレアか！そうかそうだね。三期生お姉さん組で歌うの？
Oh, Flare! Oh, I see. Are the Gen 3 older sister group going to sing?
よし、ちょっとおめかししなきゃ、ちょっと。
Alright, I have to dress up a bit.
ドキドキ、え、何々？
My heart's racing, wait, what?
おい、ノエフレ時代は終わったんだよ！
Hey, the NoeFlare era is over!
えー！
What!
これからはマリフレの時代です！
From now on, it's the MariFlare era!
イエーイ！いや、なんでおめかしする必要あるの？
Yay! Wait, why do you need to dress up?
おめかし、いやまあ、別に、社交辞令みたいな感じで。
Dressing up, well, just like a social courtesy.
え、じゃあ団長がもっと可愛くしてあげる。
Oh, then Danchou will make you even cuter.
え、何々？可愛くする？
Eh, what? Make me cuter?
これ以上可愛くなったら、いよいよ...
If I get any cuter, finally...
いよいよかな。
Finally, huh.
よいしょよいしょ。いいの、ノエちゃん、これ以上可愛くなっちゃって...
Heave-ho, heave-ho. Is it okay, Noe-chan, getting even cuter...
なんか、マリンさ、この前ちょっと痩せたい、みたいな言ってたよね。
Like, Marine, you said you wanted to lose a little weight recently, right?
言ってたから、団長がちょっとお肉柔らかくしてあげる。
You said that, so Danchou will make your meat a bit tender.
え、何何？いい？ちょっと...
Wait, what? Is it okay? Wait...
あ、待って！待って！ぎゃあー！
Ah, wait! Wait! Gyaa!
ごめんなさい！ごめんなさい！許してください！ごめんなさい！
Sorry! Sorry! Please forgive me! Sorry!
あれ？いやちょっと、団長... でもこの後フレア、だよね。
Huh? Wait a bit, Danchou... but after this it's Flare, right.
フレア頑張ってねー！団長応援してるからねー！
Flare, do your best! Danchou is rooting for you!
NEXT STAGE IS...
G-A-T-U-D-A-K-I ばばんがBang!
G-A-T-U-D-A-K-I Babanga Bang!
G-A-A-T-A-H-U-T-A-Y-A-M-B-A-N-G!
ギャラクシー☆ばばんがBang! おいでらっしゃい ビンゴ当たりして
Galaxy☆Babanga Bang! Welcome, hit the bingo
ギャラクシー☆ばばんがBang!
不知火フレア & 宝鐘マリン
Galaxy☆Babanga Bang!
Shiranui Flare & Houshou Marine
ときめき スマイル全開
Throbbing with excitement, full-power smiles
ギャラクシーばんばんっ！　不知火フレア＆宝鐘マリン
Galaxy Bang Bang! Shiranui Flare & Houshou Marine
ピコピコ　月まで一っ飛び
Pikopiko, fly to the moon in one go
くるくる　ヤッホイ！　一日一善
Spinning, yah-hoy! One good deed a day
元気牛乳飲んで
Drink energetic milk
グクグク　宇宙人でも
Glug-glug, even for aliens
お手軽ビームでお友達（アイヤー！）
Friends with a handy beam (Aiya!)
古今東西　想い出回ったら
East and West, through all times, if memories spin
ピンカル！アロハニホヘト
Pinkal! Aloha ni ho he to
あっぱれっぱれで
Bravo, bravo
メソメソなんて吹き飛ばそう
Let's blow away the whimpering
最初はグーでじゃんけんポン！
Rock-paper-scissors, shoot!
ドキドキ　コースター
A heart-pounding coaster
愛と勇気と夢ハリセン
A paper fan of love, courage, and dreams
ハートのターボスピードあげて（バンバン！）
Rev up the heart's turbo speed (Bang bang!)
食べよ　はしゃご　ラリホー
Let's eat, let's frolic, Lali-ho
天下御免のパスポート
A world-sanctioned passport
ドラマティックに　ロマンティックに
Dramatically, romantically
大冒険
A great adventure
感謝感激　ゲッチュひらめいちゃって
Thanks and gratitude, a lunar inspiration
（キラリン！）
(Kirarin!)
目と目が合えば
When our eyes meet
バタバタ天使がやってくる
The flustered angels come
（ゼンゼン！）
(Zen zen!)
どんまい！ほら吹いても
Don't mind! Even if you brag
ピピ　口笛吹いて
Pi-pi, blow a whistle
シャラシャラ　ぐっすり眠れば
Shara-shara, if you sleep soundly
明日は今日より未来です（ニイハオ！）
Tomorrow is more of the future than today (Ni hao!)
お菓子ショータイム
Sweets showtime
お土産はマカデミア
The souvenir is Macadamia
忘れちゃダメよ
Don't forget it
握手をしたら
If we shake hands
また会う日までごきげんよう
Until we meet again, farewell
ため息なんて（バイバイブー！）
Blow away the sighs (Bye bye boo!)
呑気にチャンピオン
A carefree champion
いつも心に金メダル
Always a gold medal in the heart
シュプレヒコール　右手をあげて（バンバン！）
A chant flight, raise your right hand (Bang bang!)
あれもこれも　たのもー
Everything, please come
どこかにあるよパラダイス
Paradise is somewhere out there
メニューは秘密　何が起こるか
The menu is a secret, what will happen
お楽しみ
is the fun part
ＧＡ　ドキドキ　ババンガバン
GA, doki doki, babangaban
ＧＡ　あたふた　ヤマンバガン
GA, atafuta, yamanbagan
想い出回ったら
If memories spin
ピンカル！アロハニホヘト
Pinkal! Aloha ni ho he to
あっぱれっぱれで
Bravo, bravo
メソメソなんて吹き飛ばそう
Let's blow away the whimpering
最初はグーでじゃんけんポン！
Rock-paper-scissors, shoot!
ドキドキ　コースター
A heart-pounding coaster
愛と勇気と夢ハリセン
A paper fan of love, courage, and dreams
ハートのターボスピードあげて（バンバン！）
Rev up the heart's turbo speed (Bang bang!)
食べよ　はしゃご　ラリホー
Let's eat, let's frolic, Lali-ho
天下御免のパスポート
A world-sanctioned passport
ドラマティックに　ロマンティックに
Dramatically, romantically
大冒険
A great adventure
ＧＡ　ドキドキ　ババンガバン
GA, doki doki, babangaban
ＧＡ　あたふた　ヤマンバガン
GA, atafuta, yamanbagan
ねぇ最後の何？
Hey, what was that at the end?
え？
Eh?
なんかこう... 艦隊みたいな
Like... like a fleet or something
聞いてないよ
I wasn't told about that
え、なんか雰囲気でポーズとるかなって
Eh, I thought we'd just pose with the atmosphere
これ、これも何？
This, what's this too?
これ？
This?
ＧＡ、ドキドキ、ババンガバン...
GA, doki doki, babangaban...
最後になって、急にキレキレで来いよ
At the end, suddenly coming at me with such sharp moves
Connected Fantasia
エブリバディついてこいよ
Everybody, keep up!
ということで、フレアと一緒に歌わせてもらいました、ありがとうフレア！
So, I got to sing with Flare, thank you Flare!
ありがとうマリン！呼んでくれて！
Thank you Marine! For inviting me!
でね、フレアと一緒に歌ったこの曲はね、
And, this song I sang with Flare is,
「ギャラクシーばんばんっ！」となっております。これね、
It's "Galaxy Bang Bang!". This one,
実はフレアと相談して決めた... 結構他の曲はね、
I actually decided it after consulting with Flare... Most of the other songs were
私の独断気味なんだけど、
pretty much my own decisions,
あははは！
Ahahaha!
この曲はね、この曲だけはフレアからね、
But this song, only this song was from Flare,
そうだね、提案があって、決まりましたね
That's right, there was a proposal, and we decided on it
フレアなんでこれにしようと？
Flare, why did you choose this one?
これさ、あのー、私が提案したのもう一個のやつもあったんだけど、
Well, there was another one I proposed as well,
これと同じ感じで... ああ！
With the same feeling as this one... Ah!
そう、一緒にだからね、ハモりも決まったんだよね
Yes, because it's together, the harmonies were also decided
ギャラクシーばんばんの方だったっけ？
Was it the Galaxy Bang Bang one?
そうそうそう！それでね、こっちにしましたということで
Yes, yes, yes! So we went with this one
フィーリングがあったんだよね
We had a feeling, right
懐かしい感じになったのかなって
I thought it would give a nostalgic feeling
懐かしアニソン、うちら懐かしアニソン歌う...
Nostalgic anime songs, we sing nostalgic anime songs...
そうなんだよね、マリンと一緒に歌うんだったら、
That's right, if I'm singing with Marine,
やっぱりなんかそういうちょっとナツメロ、アニソンみたいなの...
I thought something like those oldies, anime songs...
ねえ、うんうん
Yeah, mhm
も結構シナジーあるなって思ってたから
would have a lot of synergy
せっかくならね、そういうの歌いたいなって
I wanted to sing something like that since we have the chance
歌っちゃいました、楽しかったね！
And we sang it, it was fun!
楽しかったね！
It was fun!
この後もね、まだナツメロアニソンをね、歌いたいなと思ってはいるんですけども
Even after this, I'm still thinking I want to sing more oldies anime songs
いや、でもね、ちょっとさっきノエルちゃんが...
But, you know, just now Noel-chan was...
プンプン怒ってたけど...
pouting and angry...
まあ最後ね、ノエルちゃんが...
Well at the end, Noel-chan...
呼ばれたような気がして。
I felt like I was being called.
いや、でもどう？船長、楽しかった？
Anyway, how was it? Captain, did you have fun?
楽しかったよ！
I had fun!
楽しいね。このまま2人でライブする？
It is fun. Should the two of us just keep performing?
うん、ノエルちゃんがいれば大丈夫。
Yeah, as long as Noel-chan is here, it's fine.
つまんねぇ。ノエルちゃん？
Boring. Noel-chan?
ノエちゃん！
Noe-chan!
一緒に歌おうぜ！
Let's sing together!
黙れ！
Shut up!
イチャイチャするふれあ...
Flare is being all lovey-dovey...
一緒に...もう、もうノエル、無視しに来ました。
Together... Seriously, Noel has come to ignore us.
なんだ、じゃあ、ちょっと、これからね、
Oh, well then, from here on...
じゃあ、ノエちゃんが拗ねてるかもしれないから、一緒にノエちゃんに会いに行こうか。
...since Noe-chan might be sulking, shall we go see her together?
よし、行くか。
Alright, let's go.
じゃあ、手繋いで行こうか。
Then, let's go holding hands.
はい。
Okay.
ガチ恋！これも違う！ノエル！ガチ！
True love! This is also wrong! Noel! Seriously!
NEXT STAGE IS...
Hold me baby, 踊るよ Sunday
Hold me baby, I'll dance on Sunday
Touch me baby, 気分は Holiday
Touch me baby, feeling like a holiday
PARTY☆NIGHT
お祭り娘
Omatsuri Musume
Houshou Marine 1 Million Subscribers Anniversary LIVE
嫌なこと全部忘れちゃおう
Let's forget all the bad things
一晩眠って目覚めたらハッピーガール
Sleep for a night and wake up a happy girl
夢の途中で出会う不思議
A mystery met in the middle of a dream
悪夢を食べてるバクたちもグッドフレンド
Even the tapirs eating nightmares are good friends
いつもならばお喋りもしない
Normally we wouldn't even talk
窮屈な人も陽気なリズムで変身
Even stiff people transform with a cheerful rhythm
Hold me baby, ウキウキレディ ストレスは溜めないで
Hold me baby, cheerful lady, don't let stress build up
Touch me baby, キラキラボディ リフレッシュしよう
Touch me baby, sparkling body, let's refresh
Hold me baby, 踊るよ Sunday 心にも栄養を
Hold me baby, I'll dance on Sunday, nourish your heart too
Touch me baby, 気分は Holiday 星空のメロディ
Touch me baby, feeling like a holiday, melody of the starry sky
疲れすぎて臆病な日には
On days when you're too tired and cowardly
まぶた閉じてアクセスしてみて
Try to close your eyes and access it
ハバパーティーナイト
Have a party night
Hold me baby, ウキウキレディ ストレスは溜めないで
Hold me baby, cheerful lady, don't let stress build up
Touch me baby, キラキラボディ リフレッシュしよう
Touch me baby, sparkling body, let's refresh
Hold me baby, 踊るよ Sunday 心にも栄養を
Hold me baby, I'll dance on Sunday, nourish your heart too
Touch me baby, 気分は Holiday 星空のメロディ
Touch me baby, feeling like a holiday, melody of the starry sky
Hold me baby, ウキウキレディ
Hold me baby, cheerful lady
Touch me baby, キラキラボディ
Touch me baby, sparkling body
Hold me baby, ウキウキレディ
Hold me baby, cheerful lady
イエーイ！
Yay!
やあ、楽しかったねー。
Ah, that was fun, wasn't it?
懐かしいねー。
How nostalgic!
懐かしいよね。ちょっと、さっきのフレアから引き続きの
It is, isn't it? We continued with another nostalgic
懐かしいアニメソングでお送りしました。
anime song following the one with Flare.
デ・ジ・キャラットのね、パーティー・タイム歌いました！ありがとう！
We sang Party Time from Di Gi Charat! Thank you!
パーティー・ナイトな。
It's Party Night.
あれ？パーティー...ナイト？
Wait, Party... Night?
パーティー・ナイトだ。
It is Party Night.
失礼しました。
My apologies.
ありがとうございますー。
Thank you very much!
これはね、えっと、フレアとね、元々、最初候補にあって。
This song was a candidate from the very beginning with Flare.
そう。
Right.
いや、っていうか3人曲だし。お姉さん組だもんね。
I mean, it's a song for three. And we're the older sister group.
そうなんだよね。ってなって、ちょっとフレアじゃない、えっとノエルにもぶち込むパート...
That's right. So we decided to give a part to... not Flare, uh, Noel too...
私のこと好きすぎか？
Do you guys love me too much?
イエーイ。ぎゅー。
Yay! Hug!
怖い怖い怖い...
Scary, scary, scary...
いや、でもなんかノエちゃん、
But you know, I thought Noe-chan
てっきりまだ怒ってるのかなーって思ったけど、怒ってなくて良かった。
might still be angry, so I'm glad she's not.
怒ってるよ。
I am angry.
そんな間を置いて。
Don't say it after such a pause.
怒ってるよ。
I'm angry.
怒ってんの？
You are?
なーんでも、でも！だってフレアがいるからね、不機嫌は誤解だからね、ノエちゃんは。
Well, but! Since Flare is here, my grumpiness was just a misunderstanding.
あ、本当？誤解？
Oh, really? A misunderstanding?
そう、あれはやらされて...やらされてる。
Yeah, I was made to... made to do that.
フレアいいな。
Flare is great.
本当にお前を思ってくれる女ってのを、
A woman who really thinks of you...
見落としてるようだな、フレア。いいのかな、そんなんで。
...you seem to be overlooking her, Flare. Is that okay?
ね、この後いっぱい一緒に、
Hey, after this, lots of time together...
素敵な時を過ごそうか。ご飯でも食べるかな。
...let's spend a wonderful time. Shall we go eat?
いやてかさ、てかさ、ちょっと待って、待って。
No, but like, but like, wait a sec, wait.
いや、てか、これからはね、ちょっとみんな帰るのまだ早いから。
No, but like, from now on, it's still too early for everyone to go home.
まだ早い、そうだよ。
It's still early, that's right.
この後、まだね、3期生全員集合なんだから。
Because after this, all the 3rd gen members are gathering.
もちろん、ぺこらっちも、るしあっちも、来るに決まってるでしょ？
Of course, Pekoracchi and Rushiacchi are coming too, right?
だからちょっとね、みんな揃うからね、まだ待ってもらって。
So everyone is gathering, so please wait a bit longer.
船長これからね、るしあとかぺこらとかと、
I'm going to, with Rushia and Pekora...
これから歌おうと思いますので、うん。
...sing with them from now on.
じゃ、ちょっと、なんですか？後半なのかな、これ。
So, what is it? Is this the second half?
どの辺なのかな、わかんないけど。
I don't know where we are, but...
後半気分に、うんー。
In a second-half mood...
出航！
Set sail!
いってきまーす！せつなに、いこうね！バイバーイ！
Off I go! Let's go in an instant! Bye-bye!
NEXT STAGE IS...
嗚呼、素晴らしきニャン生
Ah, It's a Wonderful Cat's Life
歌：るしあ・宝鐘マリン
Vocals: Rushia / Houshou Marine
「これは可愛いお嬢さん
“Hello there, cute little missy.
真っ白な毛がとても素敵ね」
Your pure white fur is very lovely.”
「こんな月が綺麗な夜は
“On a night with such a beautiful moon,
僕と一緒に遊びませんか」
won't you come and play with me?”
「ニャン生は一度きり
“You only get one cat life.
楽しむが勝ちなのです」
Having fun is how you win!”
「あなたを縛る首輪は
“That collar that's binding you...
噛みちぎってあげましょう」
...I'll bite it right off for you.”
「野良は最高ニャンニャンニャン
“Being a stray is the best, nyan nyan nyan!
魚くすねて、ハト追いかけて」
Stealing fish and chasing pigeons.”
「昼間は働く人間を
“While looking down on humans...
尻目に屋根の上で夢うつつ」
...working during the day, I'm half-asleep on the roof.”
「あなたも自由にニャンニャンニャン
“You should be free too, nyan nyan nyan!
素敵な仲間も紹介しましょう」
I'll introduce you to some wonderful friends.”
「さあ、その窓を開いて
“Now, open that window...
飛び出すのです」
...and jump out!”
「これは気ままな野良猫さん
“Well, what a carefree stray cat.
闇の中目だけが光ってる」
Only your eyes are shining in the darkness.”
「随分口が上手だけど
“You're quite the smooth talker,
私は馬鹿な女じゃないわ」
but I'm no foolish woman.”
「ニャン生は一度きり
“You only get one cat life.
だからこそ飼われるのよ」
That's why I'd rather be kept.”
「ブランド首輪の価値が
“The value of a brand-name collar...
あなたにはわかるかしら」
...do you think you can understand it?”
「私は優雅ニャンニャンニャン
“I'm elegant, nyan nyan nyan!
美味しい食事に、ふかふかベッド」
Delicious meals and a fluffy bed.”
「水はちょっぴり苦手だけど
“I'm a bit bad with water,
毎日シャワーだって浴びれるの」
but I can even take a shower every day.”
「それに比べてニャンニャンニャン
“Compared to that, nyan nyan nyan!
あなたは誰に守ってもらうの？」
Who is going to protect you?”
「明日車に轢かれるかも
“You might get run over by a car tomorrow,
知れないじゃない」
you know.”
「そんな強気なとこも素敵です」
“Even that stubborn side of you is wonderful.”
「いっそあなたを好きになりました」
“I've actually come to like you.”
「あら正直ね、でもそんなやり方じゃ」
“Oh, how honest. But with that kind of approach...
「心揺らがないわ」
...you won't move my heart.”
「僕の夢はニャンニャンニャン
“My dream is, nyan nyan nyan!
いつかはこの街を飛び出して」
To jump out of this town someday...
「はるか北の国に旅して
Travel to a far-off northern country,
オーロラをこの目で見ることです」
and see the aurora with my own eyes.”
「そこにあなたがニャンニャンニャン
“If you were there with me, nyan nyan nyan,
いてくれたらなんて素敵でしょう」
how wonderful would it be?”
「だけどそれは叶わないらしい」
“But it seems that won't come true.”
「生き方はニャンニャンニャン
“A way of life, nyan nyan nyan...
そう簡単には変えられないの」
...it's not so easily changed.”
「それに私を飼っている
“Besides, I can't leave the girl...
女の子を一人にできないわ」
...who's keeping me all alone.”
「話の途中よニャンニャンニャン
“I'm not finished talking yet, nyan nyan nyan!
あらもう行っちゃうの？ねえちょっと！」
Oh, are you leaving already? Hey, wait!”
「明日の朝もここに来て
“You can come here tomorrow morning too.
いいのよ 待ってるから」
I'll be waiting for you.”
はい、というわけで、るしあが歌ってくれました！るしあ、可愛かった〜！
So, Rushia sang for us! Rushia was so cute!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
やばかったね。
It was amazing.
そう、ということで、るしあとの曲は、「嗚呼、素晴らしきニャン生」にしました。
So, for the song with Rushia, we chose "Ah, Subarashiki Nyansei."
3年越し？
Three years in the making?
はい。ちょっとこれは船長のチョイスで。
Yes. This was the Captain's choice.
なんでこの曲にしたかというとね、やっぱり船長の中でるしあって結構猫のイメージ...
As for why I chose this song, well, in the Captain's mind, Rushia has quite a cat-like image...
おや？
Oh?
ある。おや？おや？
I have one. Oh? Oh?
おや、猫なのでしょう？にゃん、にゃんにゃん。
Oh, so I'm a cat? Meow, meow meow.
可愛い、るしお！
So cute, Rushio!
で、猫っぽいねって思ってて、で、そんなちょっと高飛車というか、なんか飼われて綺麗な猫ちゃんのるしあを、こう口説きに行く僕、みたいなのが見たかったのね。
And, I thought she's very cat-like, and, I wanted to see myself going to woo a slightly haughty, or like, a beautiful pet cat version of Rushia.
口説きたかったのね。
You wanted to woo me.
そう、口説きたかったの。だからちょっと今回はこの曲にいたしましたと。
Yes, I wanted to woo you. So that's why I chose this song this time.
ありがとう。この曲はね、そんなにマリンがるしあのことを考えてくれた曲なんだね。
Thank you. So this song is one that Marine put that much thought into Rushia for.
そうだよ、るしあ。にゃん猫るしあ可愛かったな〜。
That's right, Rushia. Meow-cat Rushia was so cute~.
可愛かった？やった！嬉しい。
Was I cute? Yay! I'm happy.
はい、るしあの...
Yes, Rushia's...
マリンの、スパダリ具合も見れて、るしあ良かった。
I was also able to see Marine's... "Super Darling" side, so Rushia is glad.
にゃん猫のるしあ、もうずっとにゃんにゃんしてほしいな、るしあに。
I want nyan-cat Rushia to keep meowing forever, Rushia.
本当？
Really?
え、行くにゃん、にゃん、マリンにゃんにゃん。にゃんにゃんにゃんにゃんにゃんにゃんにゃん...
Er, here I go, nyan, nyan, Marine nyan nyan. Meow meow meow...
あああああああ！
Aaaaaaa!
え？あ？マリィ！マリィ！マリィが！マリィが息絶え絶えじゃない！マリン、マリン！
Eh? Ah? Marie! Marie! Marie! Marie is... she's barely breathing! Marine, Marine!
これはネクロマンスしなきゃ。にゃんにゃん、マリン生き返れにゃん！もう、マリンにゃんにゃん生き返れにゃん！マリィマリィマリィ！
I have to use necromancy. Meow meow, Marine, come back to life nyan! Come on, Marine meow meow come back to life nyan! Marie Marie Marie!
うわああ！ネクロマンサー最強！
Whoa! Necromancer is the strongest!
生き返った！
You're back to life!
よー、るしあありがとう。るしあが可愛すぎるおかげで生き返りました。
Yo, Rushia thank you. Thanks to Rushia being too cute, I came back to life.
や、可愛くて可愛くて生き返っちゃうるしあしか。るしあパンパワーだ。
Yeah, only Rushia can make me come back to life by being so cute. It's Rushia-pan power.
カカ！カカ！
Haha! Kaka!
あ〜、可愛い、るしあ。
Ah, cute Rushia.
幸せだな、マリン。
I'm so happy, Marine.
幸せだね、るしあ。
We're happy, aren't we, Rushia.
るしあさ、うん、今この時間がすごく幸せなんだよね。
Rushia is, yeah, really happy in this moment.
や、わかるよ。船長もだよ。
Yeah, I get it. Captain is too.
うん、本当？いつもマリンって浮気ばかりするけど...
Yeah, really? Marine is always flirting with others, though...
ん？ん？ん？
Eh? Eh? Eh?
にゃにゃにゃにゃにゃにゃ。今るしあしか見えとらん。るしあしか勝たん。あ〜もう本当にこれはもう何も言うことないわ。
Nya nya nya nya nya nya. I can only see Rushia right now. Rushia is the best. Ah, really, I have nothing more to say.
マリィ、うん。
Marie, yeah.
今さこの幸せな時間にさ、一緒に...死の？
Now, in this happy moment, let's... die together?
ちょっと待って、るしあ。
Wait a minute, Rushia.
マリィ、なんで逃げるの？待って待って。
Marie, why are you running away? Wait, wait.
ちょっとちょっとちょっとそれ何それ何ちょっとちょっとちょっと...
Wait, wait, wait, what is that, what is that, wait, wait, wait...
マリィにゃん！逃がさないよ。ダメだよ。はい、一緒にしよう。
Marine-nyan! I won't let you escape. You can't. Come on, let's do it together.
るしあ！やめて！助けて！助けて！
Rushia! Stop! Help! Help!
ダメダメ。なんで逃げるの？なんで逃げるの？嘘つき嘘つき人間...
No, no. Why are you running? Why are you running? Liar, liar human...
NEXT STAGE IS...
ココロぴょんぴょん 待ちがえるふりして もちょっと近づいちゃえ
My heart is jumping! I'll pretend I'm waiting and get a little bit closer.
簡単には教えない こんなに好きなことは 内緒なの
I won't tell you so easily. The fact that I like you this much is a secret.
ふわふわドキドキ 内緒ですよ はじめが肝心 つんだつんだ
Fluffy and heart-throbbing, it's a secret. The beginning is important! Stacked up!
フラフラドキドキ 内緒だって イタズラ笑顔で ぴょんぴょん
Dizzy and heart-throbbing, I said it's a secret! With a mischievous smile, hop, hop.
扉開けたとたん 見知らぬ世界へと
The moment the door opens, into an unknown world.
そんなのないぺこ！ アンビリーない！
There's no such thing peko! Unbelieva-no!
それが有りえるかも ミルク色の異次元
But that might actually happen, in a milk-colored alternate dimension.
コーヒーカップ 覗いたら
When I peeked into the coffee cup,
私が私を 見つめてました なんで？なんで？
I was staring at myself. Why? Why?
ふたりは困りますね
Having two of me is a problem.
うそ！おんなじ趣味？ 誰を見つめるの 君でしょ！
No way! Same hobbies? Who are you looking at? You, of course!
君だけ見てるよ
I'm only looking at you.
これは夢？ カップの夢 飲み干しておしまい
Is this a dream? A dream in a cup. Drink it all up and that's it.
いつもぴょんぴょん 可能楽しさ求めて もちょっと弾けちゃえ
Always jumping! Seeking possible fun, let's pop a little more.
一緒なら素敵だい 君に言わせたいから（言いなさい！）
It's wonderful if we're together. Because I want to make you say it (Say it!)
ココロぴょんぴょん 待ちがえるふりして もちょっと近づいちゃえ
My heart is jumping! I'll pretend I'm waiting and get a little bit closer.
簡単には教えない こんなに好きなことは （好きだってことはわわわ！） 内緒なの
I won't tell you so easily. The fact that I like you this much (That I like you-wa-wa-wa!) is a secret.
ふわふわドキドキ 内緒ですよ はじめが肝心 つんだつんだ
Fluffy and heart-throbbing, it's a secret. The beginning is important! Stacked up!
ふわふわドキドキ 内緒だって イタズラ笑顔で ぴょんぴょん
Fluffy and heart-throbbing, I said it's a secret! With a mischievous smile, hop, hop.
日常の中にも 不思議の交差点
Even in everyday life, there's a crossroads of wonders.
それならあるね アンビリーない
Well, those exist. Unbelieva-no.
ありえない角度に 切り分けたケーキが
A cake sliced at an impossible angle.
いたずらうさぎ 呼んじゃったよ
It called over a mischievous rabbit.
私も私と 驚きました なんで？なんで？
I was surprised at myself too. Why? Why?
喋るうさぎ 嘘？マジ！
A talking rabbit? No way! Seriously!
困りましたね お茶を飲んだら
It's quite a problem. After drinking some tea,
ついに見つけたよ 君への 君との運命
I finally found it. My destiny for you, with you.
いろいろ夢 恋の夢 初めてのときめき
Various dreams, dreams of love. My first heart-throb.
んな歌好きに
...such songs...
ぺしながらはにかんで
...shuffling while smiling shyly.
三・二・一・ハイ!
Three, two, one, hi!
一緒なら無敵だい
Together we're invincible.
本音隠せなくなる
Can't hide our true feelings anymore.
(本音だ!)
(It's my true feeling!)
明日ランラン希望
Tomorrow, ran-ran hope.
今すぐ会いたいなはにかんで
Want to see you right now, smiling shyly.
三・二・一・ハイ!
Three, two, one, hi!
一瞬だけ耳もと
Just for a moment, in your ear...
本当は好きなんだと
...saying I actually like you.
(好きなんだ!)
(I like you!)
つまりななななささやく
In other words, whispering na-na-na-na.
これは夢
This is a dream.
カップの夢
A dream in a cup.
飲み干しておねがい
Drink it all up, please.
いつもぴょんぴょん可能
Always hopping, it's possible.
楽しさ求めて
Seeking out fun,
もうちょっと弾けちゃえ
let's pop a little more.
一緒なら素敵だい
Together it's wonderful.
君に言わせたいから
Because I want to make you say it.
(言いなさい!)
(Say it!)
心ぴょんぴょん待ち
My heart is waiting, hopping,
考えるふりして
pretending to think,
もうちょっと近づいちゃえ
let's get a little closer.
簡単には教えない
I won't tell you so easily
こんなに好きなことは
that I like you this much.
(内緒だよ!)
(It's a secret!)
恋の夢
A dream of love.
好きなんだつまりななな
I like you, in other words na-na-na.
ふわふわドキドキ内緒ですよ
Fluffy and heart-pounding, it's a secret.
初めが肝心つなつんだ
The beginning is vital, it's all set.
ふわふわドキドキ内緒だって
Fluffy and heart-pounding, I said it's a secret.
いたずら笑顔でぴょんぴょん!
With a mischievous smile, hop, hop!
はははー!ということで、
Hahaha! So there you have it,
ぺこらちゃんが来てくれました!ぺこら!
Pekora-chan is here! Pekora!
いえーい!あ、ぺこら!
Yeeeah! Ah, Pekora!
ありがとー!
Thank you!
ありがとー。
Thank you.
ありがとーぺこ!
Thank you, peko!
飛びすぎたぺこね。
I jumped too much, peko.
ね、飛びすぎたね。
Yeah, you jumped too much.
いやでも可愛かった、ぴょんぴょん跳ねる
But it was cute seeing Pekora
ぺこらが見れて。いやね、今回この曲、
hopping around. Well, this song,
Daydream caféっていうね、ごちうさの曲なんだけども。
Daydream café, it's a Gochiusa song.
これね、もうどうしてもぺこらが歌ってる...
I really, really wanted to hear Pekora singing...
ちょっと息切れ半端ない。
I'm out of breath.
ぺこらが歌ってるの聴きたくて、
I wanted to hear Pekora singing it,
ちょっと一緒に歌っちゃいました。ぺこら、どうですか?
so we sang it together. Pekora, how was it?
嬉しかったぺこだよ!
I was happy, peko!
マリンとね、歌えたのもすっごい嬉しかったぺこだけど。
Singing with Marine made me super happy, peko, but...
結構ね...
Marine...
やめろぺこ。
Yeah, stop it, peko.
Daydream caféね、ぺこらやっぱ兎田ぺこらだから、
Daydream café is like, because I'm Usada Pekora,
「歌って歌って」って実はずっと多かったぺこなの。
I actually had many requests to sing it, peko.
いや絶対、ぺこらの声で聴きたいもん、船長も。
Totally! Even Senchou wanted to hear it in Pekora's voice.
聴けたもん今日。やったー!
I heard it today! Yay!
いえーい。いや、そうだからぺこらも嬉しかったし、めちゃ楽しかった。
Yay. Yeah, so Pekora was happy too, it was super fun.
いやもうこれを機にね、Daydream café覚えたと思うから、
Since we've learned Daydream café now,
ね、オケもね、作ってもらったから、ぺこら今後歌枠とかでぜひ歌ってね。
we had the accompaniment made, so sing it in your streams too!
オッケーぺこ!
Okay, peko!
それもそうなんだけど、
That too, but...
最近さ...
Lately...
ペコマリのさ、ファンアートってなんかちょっと増えてない?ぺこら。
Pekomari fanart has been increasing, don't you think, Pekora?
いや、あんまりそんなに二人でコラボしてないぺこだよね。
Well, we don't really collab just the two of us that much, peko.
なんでそんな、急に冷たくなっちゃって、どうしたの?
Why are you being so cold all of a sudden? What's wrong?
冷たい!冷たいけど!今日ちょっと2メートル以内で近づけないから、
It's cold! Cold! But today we can't get within 2 meters of each other,
ちょっと距離あるけど、ぺこら...ぺこら...
so there's distance, but Pekora... Pekora...
いやでもね、おま、船長とぺこーらのあんまり二人きりのコラボって
But really, Marine and Pekora don't collab just the two of us
そんなにしてないぺこだけど、確かに。
that much, but it's true.
そうだよね。
Right.
多いんだよね、なんか増えてるよね。
There's a lot, it's increasing.
そうそう。だからね、最近ね、なんか
Exactly. So lately, like,
「ぺこらが船長を実は好きで」とかね、
"Pekora actually likes Senchou",
「船長がぺこらをナンパしたらぺこらがドキドキしてて」とかよく見るのね。
or "If Senchou hits on Pekora, she gets flustered", I see that a lot.
それを見た結果、どうなったかと言いますと、
And as a result of seeing those, I thought...
あれ?もしかして船長って、
"Wait, am I, Senchou..."
ぺこらちゃんとお付き合いしてる?
"...dating Pekora-chan?"
ねえ、あんた誰にでもそういうこと言うぺこだからさ!
Hey, you say that kind of thing to everyone, peko!
だれとでも付き合えれば付き合いたいじゃないか!
But I want to date whoever I can!
あんた、やめなさいよ!いろんな女に手出ししまくるの、やめなさいぺこ!
Cut it out! Stop hitting on all kinds of women, peko!
いやでもそんなぺこら、今日冷たいけどさ。
Even if Pekora is cold today...
でもさ、ちょっと、今日見えます?ちょっと、上。
look up there. Can you see it? Above us.
宝鐘マリン100万人記念ライブ。
Houshou Marine 1 Million Subscribers Anniversary Live.
いや、おめでとうぺこ、マリン!本当おめでとうぺこからね!
Congratulations, peko, Marine! Really congrats on 1 million!
いやちょっと、100万人っていうさ、ちょっとお祝いというか権限というか、
Well, using this 1 million subscribers celebration, or rather authority...
ねえ?
Right?
それを使って、ぺこらちゃん、今日はデレデレぺこらちゃんになってください!
I'll use it... Pekora-chan, today please be "Dere-Dere" Pekora-chan!
リバースカードオープン!「兎田ぺこら100万人」カードを発動!
Reverse Card Open! Usada Pekora 1 Million Subscriber Card activation!
え、そんな...これは、貴様の持ってる権限を全て無効にする!
Wait! What!? This makes all your authority null and void!
そんなわけで、バイバイ!じゃあね!
Because of that, bye bye! See ya!
こんな、どうでもいいことに使うな!ぺこら!そんなんでいいんかい100万人!
Don't use it for something so trivial! Pekora! Is that okay for 1 million!?
NEXT STAGE IS...
重ねた手をぎゅっと離さずに
Holding our joined hands tightly without letting go...
行こうよ 行こうよ
Let's go, let's go...
夢見る空へ
ホロライブファンタジー
To the Dreamy Sky
Hololive Fantasy
夢見る空へ
To the dreamy sky
窓越しに見上げた
I looked up through the window
縦の小さな空
At the small, vertical sky
ここで出会えたのは
Meeting everyone here
数えきれない奇跡
Is an uncountable miracle
繰り返した一歩が
Every step we took
キラリ希望繋いで
Connected us to sparkling hope
星のような笑顔
Smiles like the stars
導いた
Guided us
Day by day
みんなの声が力になる
Everyone's voices become our strength
Step by step
ここでそれぞれ目指すもの
What each of us aims for here
それぞれ描くもの
What each of us draws
それぞれ願った夢
The dreams each of us wished for
重ねた手はギュッと離さずに
Keep our hands joined tight and don't let go
一人一人違う色で
With each person's different color
描き出すトキメキ
We draw out our excitement
振り向くことなく真っすぐに
Going straight ahead without looking back
行くよ
Let's go
行こう
夢見る空へ
To the dreamy sky
笑い合ったことや
The things we laughed about
尽きそうにない話題
And topics that never seem to end
思い出いっぱいなのに
Even though we have so many memories
あと一歩の毎日
Every day is one step away
上書きじゃなくって
Not just overwriting it
名前つけて保存
But saving it with a name
全部全部大事で
Everything is so important
いとおしくなる
It all becomes so dear
One for all
みんなのためが力になる
For everyone's sake, it becomes our strength
All for one
今日も賑やかすぎるくらい
Today as well, it's almost too lively
笑顔がもう止まらない
The smiles just won't stop
想いは膨らんでいく
Our feelings continue to grow
重ねた今 ギュッと噛みしめた
I savor this shared moment
一人一人違う声で
With each person's different voice
歌声は広がる
Our singing voices spread out
風を感じたら真っすぐに
If you feel the wind, go straight ahead
行くよ
Let's go
行こう
夢見る空へ
To the dreamy sky
憧れて手を伸ばし
Yearning and reaching out my hand
掴み取ったその光が
The light that I grasped...
いつかまた誰かの憧れに変わる
...will someday become someone else's yearning
繋げよう
Let's connect them
重ねた手はギュッと離さずに
Keep our hands joined tight and don't let go
一人一人違う色で
With each person's different color
描き出すトキメキ
We draw out our excitement
出会えたすべてにありがとう
Thank you for everything we've encountered
軌跡なぞって明日へ
Following the path toward tomorrow
ずっとそばにいるよ
I'll always be by your side
行くよ
Let's go
行こう
夢見る空へ
To the dreamy sky
今のトークテーマ：特になし
Current talk theme: None in particular
Find a reason to sing 君に会いたい
Find a reason to sing, I want to meet you
歌うことを教えてくれた君に
To you, who taught me how to sing
Connecting
ホロライブファンタジー
Hololive Fantasy
誰かが零すメロディーを
Someone spills a melody
誰かが拾って また誰かが運んでく
Someone picks it up, and someone else carries it on
名前も顔もわからない
I don't know your name or your face
繋がる奇跡が 誰かを幸せにする
But the connected miracle makes someone happy
眺め 羨んでばかりいた 今までは
...staring and doing nothing but being envious until now.
Finally, it's time to sing 君と歌えば
Finally, it's time to sing with you...
時間も忘れ 夢中になれたんだ
I forgot the time and became absorbed in it.
Finally, it's time to sing たった一つも
Finally, it's time to sing even just one thing...
神様に与えられた贈り物
A gift from God.
Connecting, connecting with your song
Connecting, connecting with your dream
Connecting, connecting with your life
Connecting with you
僕らは何と戦い 何に敗れて
What have we fought, what have we lost to,
何を失ってきただろう
and what have we lost?
名前も顔もわからない 歪んだ言葉が
Distorted words from people whose names and faces are unknown
誰かの日常を奪う
steal someone's daily life.
永遠に通じ合うことはないと
I thought we would never understand each other forever,
思ってた 今までは
until now.
Finally, it's time to sing 君と歌えば
Finally, it's time to sing with you...
一人じゃないと 初めて感じたんだ
I felt for the first time that I wasn't alone.
Finally, it's time to sing いつか話そう
Finally, it's time to sing let's talk someday...
ちゃんと目を見て 初めましてを言うよ
I'll look you in the eye and say "nice to meet you".
Connecting, connecting with your song
Connecting, connecting with your dream
Connecting, connecting with your life
Connecting with you
Everything to have fun Be my liner その乾いた日常に 夢を問おう
Everything to have fun Be my liner. Let's ask about dreams in that dry daily life.
Everything a little crazy Be my liner その感情のままに 投げつけろ アップロード
Everything a little crazy Be my liner. Throw it as it is with that emotion, Upload.
どうして人は 巡り会うのだろう
Why do people meet each other?
こうして笑って 祝って繋がって
Laughing, celebrating, and connecting like this.
そして次は 何が起きるのかな
And what will happen next?
誰かの叫ぶ声がする
I hear someone shouting,
行き場をなくした あの頃の僕のように
like me back then who had nowhere to go.
名前も顔もわからない 君の優しさに
How much have I been saved by your kindness,
どれだけ救われただろう
even though I don't know your name or face?
画面越し手を伸ばし
Reaching out through the screen,
次は僕が誰かを
next, I'll be...
繋げる番だ
...the one to connect someone.
Connecting!
Finally, it's time to sing 僕と歌おう
Finally, it's time to sing let's sing together...
時間を忘れ 夢中になれるなら
If we can forget the time and get absorbed in it.
Finally, it's time to sing それはきっとね
Finally, it's time to sing it must be...
神様に与えられた贈り物
A gift from God.
Finally, it's time to sing 君に会いたい
Finally, it's time to sing I want to see you...
歌うこと 教えてくれた君に
To you, who taught me how to sing.
Finally, it's time to sing 一緒に歌おう
Finally, it's time to sing let's sing together...
何もないけど 君への贈り物
I have nothing, but this is a gift for you.
Connecting, connecting with your song
Connecting, connecting with your dream
Connecting, connecting with your life
Connecting with you
Connecting, connecting with your song
Connecting, connecting with your dream
Connecting, connecting with your life
Connecting with you
はい！というわけで！
Alright! So!
イェーイ！
Yay!
3期生みんなで「Connecting」でした！ありがとうございました！
That was "Connecting" by all of the 3rd generation! Thank you very much!
いやーもうめちゃくちゃ久しぶりにね、みんなで揃って...
Wow, it's been such a long time since we all gathered like this...
これ思い出の曲やから、うちらの。ね！
This is a song of memories for us. Right!
ねー！
Right!
懐かしいぺこね！
It brings back memories, peko!
Connecting歌ったの思い出すね。ちょっとね、前回の豊洲で歌った時とはね、
I remember singing "Connecting". It's a bit different from when we sang it at Toyosu last time,
パートがっつり変えて...
we changed the parts completely...
シャウトとかもね、ちょっとペコるしちゃんに、やってもらいました。
and for the shouts and such, I had Pekorushi-chan do them.
どう、どうだった？すごかった？シャウト。
How was it? Was it amazing? The shouts.
いや戦ってたぺこね。めちゃめちゃ...
Well, we were fighting, peko. Very much...
声高いからな、二人とも。バッチリ。
Both of them have high voices. Perfect.
うん、めっちゃいい感じだったよ。
Yeah, it felt really good.
うん、かっこよかった。
Yeah, it was cool.
初号機来てた、初号機。
Unit-01 was here, Unit-01.
エペコら可愛かった。
Epekora was cute.
初号機ね、ちょっと、ちょっと可愛子ぶった初号機。
Unit-01, right. A slightly, slightly cute-acting Unit-01.
結構ガチだったけどねｗ
It was quite serious though (laughs).
宝鐘マリン100万人記念ライブ Connected Fantasia
Houshou Marine 1 Million Subscribers Commemorative Live: Connected Fantasia
...だったけどね。あっても可愛かったのね。
...but they were still cute either way.
や、ということで。
Anyway...
せっかくね、5人揃ってアイドル衣装着てるから...
Since all five of us are together in our idol outfits...
うん。
Yeah.
ちょっとこれはさ、記念にさ、
Why don't we do a little something to commemorate this?
ちょっとね、なんか撮影会とか少しだけしませんか？
How about we have a quick little photoshoot?
いいね！やろうやろう！いいねー！
Sounds great! Let's do it! That's a good idea!
やりましょうよ！やろう！やろう！
Let's do it! Let's do it!
じゃあね、ちょっと、ここは...
Okay, so...
うーん。いつもだったらよくカメラマンがさ、いてさ、
Usually, there's a photographer who tells us what to do,
「どんなポーズして」とかあるけど...
like "Strike this pose" and stuff...
ちょっとそれぞれ我々がやってみたいポーズ、
But since all five of us are here, I thought we should try
5人揃ったからにはやりたい、みたいなポーズをやってみようかなと。
the poses we've always wanted to do together.
うんうん。
Right, right.
じゃあ船長から。
Let's start with me.
おっ。
Oh.
船長ね。
Senchou's first.
なんかね、みんな揃ったらね、したかったの。うん。
There's something I've wanted to do if we all got together.
扇！
A human fan!
本当にそれやりたかったの？扇？
You really wanted to do that? A fan?
意外と体育会系。
That's surprisingly athletic.
ちょっと行くよ、みんな。
Okay, here we go, everyone.
みんな体育会系の意地を見せつけるのよ、うちらの。
Let's show them our athletic spirit!
あー。
Ah...
こうして...
Like this...
待って。
Wait.
こうして...
Like this...
こうか？
Like this?
おっ。
Oh.
おー、すごいすごいすごい！おー！
Oh, wow, wow, wow!
なんじゃこれ！
What is this?!
せーの！
One, two...!
はあー！
Hyaaah!
端っこ、待って、端っこが辛そう。
The ones on the ends, wait, they look like they're struggling.
みんな大丈夫？
Is everyone okay?
端っこが辛そう、端っこが辛そう。
The ends look painful, they look really painful.
船長だけ、ごめん、なんか一人だけ楽をさせてもらってすいませんでした。
Sorry that I was the only one who had it easy. My bad.
これちょっとズルかったかな、これは。自分が真ん中っていうのは。
It was a bit unfair for me to be right in the middle.
あの、今回ね、あの、主役マリンだから。真ん中でいいんだよ。
Well, Marine is the star today. So it's fine for you to be in the center.
そうね。
That's right.
いいんですか？すいません、ありがとうございます。
Is that okay? Sorry, thank you so much.
え、なんかみんなはさ、せっかく5人揃ったから
Do the rest of you have any poses you want to try
なんかしてみたいポーズとかないの？
now that we're all together?
じゃあ、はい！ほい！
Okay then, me!
やっぱ戦隊ものをやろうよ。
We've gotta do a superhero team pose!
戦隊もの！いいねー。
A team pose! Sounds good.
うーん、じゃあ...レッド！
Hmm, okay then... Red!
ブルー！
Blue!
え、あ、これに行くの？付属していく。
Oh, are we going with that? I'll follow along.
イエロー！
Yellow!
あ、シルバー！
Oh, Silver!
ペコラ！
Pekora!
グリーン！
Green!
るしあ、悩んでる。るしあ。
Rushia's hesitating. Rushia!
るしあどうしようかな。
I wonder what Rushia should do.
我ら、
We are...
ホロライブ・ファンタジー！
Hololive Fantasy!
ここで炎がドカン。
This is where the flames go BOOM.
やってくれ、編集でなんかなりませんか。
Please make it happen. Can we fix it in post?
いや、どう？ちょっとこれ、みんな記念撮影してくれたかな？
So, how was it? Did everyone get a good shot?
あ、撮ってくれたかな。
I hope they did.
アイドル衣装なのに。
Even though we're in idol outfits.
たしかに。でもなんかさ、逆にさ、このユニフォーム感が、
True. But on the other hand, the uniform look
お揃い感が戦隊ものっぽくも。
and being in sync makes it feel like a team pose.
ああ、たしかに。そうね。
Oh, you're right. Yeah.
本当に揃ってる、みんな。ちょっと。
Everyone's really in sync. Just a bit.
いや、ほら、レンジャーとかね。
Like a team of rangers.
レンジャーとか。
Like rangers.
女の子もののやつね。あ、ね？そうそう。
Like the magical girl ones. Right? Exactly.
そういうことです。あとは？
That's right. Anything else?
ぺこらはなんかある？
Pekora, do you have one?
うーん、そうだなぁ。
Hmm, let's see...
え、なんかあれみんな知ってる？
Hey, do you guys know that one?
あの、みんなさ、頭を相手の、
Where everyone puts their head
ここ、太ももに乗せて...
on the other person's lap...
どういうこと？
What do you mean?
椅子みたいな感じ。
Like a human chair.
椅子みたいな感じ。だから...
Like a chair. So...
わかったわかった！わかった。わかった、マリンちゃん。
I get it, I get it! I understand, Marine-chan.
ちょっと待って、やってやって。
Hold on, let's try it.
え、なんかさ、こうやってさ、
Like, we do this...
あーっ！恥ずかしくない？
Ahhh! Isn't this embarrassing?
あ、そういうことか。あ、倒れていいのね。
Oh, I see. So we can lean back.
座っていいの？
Can we sit?
え、なんかこう、いや、こうやるんだよ。
No, it's like this.
こうだけど、ここに...
Like this, but then here...
あーっ、恥ずかしい！
Ahhh, how embarrassing!
それで、頭をマリン、
And then your head, Marine...
ノエルの頭がマリンに行って...
Noel's head goes on Marine...
で、マリンの頭がるしあの太ももに行って、みたいな感じで。
And then Marine's head goes on Rushia's lap, like that.
もちろん、おいで。
Of course, come here.
あたしは？
What about me?
フレアを支えなきゃ。
You have to support Flare.
円になって。これ、円になってる？
Make a circle. Are we in a circle?
円になって、これ。ちょっと、ちょっと...
Let's make a circle. Hold on, hold on...
あ、円ね。
Oh, a circle.
円ね。なるほど、察した察した。円ね。
A circle. Okay, I get it now. A circle.
これ絆が、あれだから。
This is going to test our bond.
ためされる、ためされる。
It's a real test!
こーわい！
Scary!
これわかりづらいよ！
This is hard to understand!
じゃなくて、じゃなくて。
No, that's not it.
円になって、お互いに、あれよ。
Make a circle and lean on each other.
太ももに頭を乗せ合って。
Rest your heads on each other's laps.
ねぇ、ぺこら。
Hey, Pekora...
本当にこれやるの？
Are we really doing this?
ぺこら、無理だよ！
Pekora, we can't!
せーの！
One, two...!
あーっ！無理！
Ahhh! We can't do it!
るしあが、まだ。早かったみたい。
It looks like it was still too early for Rushia.
早い！
Too early!
うちらにはまだ早かった。
It was still too early for us.
いずれやろうな、いずれ。
Let's try it again someday.
修行して。
After some training.
いや、でも今、円の形になったら、めっちゃ円陣組みたくなったからね。
But seeing us in a circle made me really want to huddle up.
あ、そうだね。
Ah, true.
円陣組んどくか。
Shall we huddle?
いや、後で最後に組もう。
No, let's save that for the very end.
ちょっとその前に。
But before that...
じゃあ、るしあはなんかしてみたいやつある？
Rushia, is there one you want to try?
えー、
Uh...
なんかしてみたいこと？
Something I want to do?
そう、5人揃ってしてみたかったこととかない？
Yeah, like something you've wanted to do with all five of us.
5人でしてみたかったことか。
Something I've wanted to do with all five of us...
え、じゃあ、みんなで、お姉さんポーズしよう。
Well then, let's all do a "big sister" pose.
いいよ。
Okay.
お姉さんポーズ。
A big sister pose.
べ、別に、なんか、小さいから紛れ込みたいとかじゃなくて、
It's not like I want to blend in because I'm small or anything,
るしあもお姉さんぽく、こう、なんか。
but I want to look like a big sister too, like this.
でもダチョウが、ダチョウが、ダチョウが。
But you're doing an ostrich, an ostrich, an ostrich!
見える？見える？
Can you see? Can you see?
親切にも支えてあげてます！
I'm kindly supporting her!
ほら、見えてますか？見えてますか？
Look, can you see? Can you see?
こんな感じで、ちょっとどうですか？
Like this, how's that?
ね、ちょっと... いいよいいよ...
Hey, wait... Nice, nice...
ほらぺこら、もっと出てきていいんだよ、前に。
Hey Pekora, you can come out more to the front.
もっと圧な照れないで、はいはい、もっと前でいいんだよ。
Don't be shy with the pressure, yes, yes, further forward is fine.
あ、ペコちゃん、なに？
Ah, Peko-chan, what?
あ、いいいね、決まった。いいんじゃない？
Ah, nice, it's set. Isn't it good?
これで大人になったかな？
Did I become an adult with this?
触ってんだよね。
You're touching me, aren't you?
どさくさに紛れて。
In the confusion.
ごめんね、ノエルちゃんの前で。
Sorry, in front of Noel-chan.
よし！じゃあ、そんなところで...
Alright! Then, on that note...
じゃあ最後にね、あの曲をちょっとみんなでやらないと...
So finally, if we don't all do that song together...
終われないなと思っておりますので。
I feel like we can't end it.
じゃあみんな、準備はいいよね？ちょっとじゃあ、円陣組んでさ...
Then everyone, you're ready, right? Let's form a circle and...
それじゃあ行くぞ！
Here we go!
エンジン組んで、組んで...
Form a circle, form it...
何にしようかな？えーと...
What should we say? Let's see...
ホロライブファンタジー、んー、おファンタジー！で行こう。
Hololive Fantasy, mmm, O-Fantasy! Let's go with that.
いいのか？ダサいんじゃないの？
Is that okay? Isn't it lame?
いくよ！いっせーのーで！
Ready! One, two!
ホロライブファンタジー！うーん、おファンタジー！
Hololive Fantasy! Mmm, O-Fantasy!
む、むずい。もう一回。
That was hard. One more time.
いっせーのーで！
One, two!
ホロライブファンタジー！うーん、おファンタジー！
Hololive Fantasy! Mmm, O-Fantasy!
何叫んでんだろう。
What are we shouting?
やめてやめて、正気に戻らないで。
Stop it, don't come back to your senses.
海賊なら Yo-ho!
If you're a pirate, Yo-ho!
Yo-ho!
踊れ叫べ Yo-ho!
Dance and shout, Yo-ho!
Yo-ho!
さあ今、旗のもとへ
Now, to the flag
宝鐘海賊団！
Houshou Pirates!
出航ー！
Set sail!
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
踊るアホイに見るアホイ！
Dancing Ahoy, watching Ahoy!
ホイホイ！
Hoi-hoi!
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
ホイホイホイ！
Hoi-hoi-hoi!
全速前進だ！
Full speed ahead!
進め (進め)
Advance (Advance)
太陽は燦々 大航海日和だ
The sun is bright, a great day for a voyage
歌え (歌え)
Sing (Sing)
最高のテンション 波の音に乗せどんぶらこ
Max tension, riding the sound of the waves, rocking
海でガールズパーティー
Girls' party at sea
陸でアニキがハッピー
Brothers are happy on land
空でハトがクルックー ヒラヒラ
Pigeons cooing in the sky, fluttering
山奥ボロボロマイハウスで夢を見て
Dreaming in my worn-out house deep in the mountains
はぁ、神様、いつかこのマリンを...
Oh, God, someday make this Marine...
...本物の海賊にしてください！
...into a real pirate!
声を上げて さあ出航だ
Raise your voice, now let's set sail
我ら宝鐘海賊団
We are the Houshou Pirates
コンパスたた手に旗を掲げ
Compass in hand, raise the flag
この海をジャックしちゃおう
Let's jack this sea
ヨーソロー 付いておいで
Yosoro! Follow us
共にYo-ho Yo-ho 叫ぼう
Let's shout Yo-ho, Yo-ho together
あぁ、最高の日々
Ah, the best days
ようこそ、我が船へ
Welcome to my ship
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
踊るアホイに見るアホイ！
Dancing Ahoy, watching Ahoy!
ホイホイ！
Hoi-hoi!
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
ホイホイホイ！
Hoi-hoi-hoi!
1、2、サンバ！サンバ！
One, two, Samba! Samba!
熱く (熱く)
Hot (Hot)
語ろうよパッション 思いを解き放て
Let's talk about passion, release your thoughts
赤く (赤く)
Red (Red)
きらめくファッション 形から入るタイプです
Sparkling fashion, I'm the type who starts with appearance
発車10秒前 走れガチ恋列車
10 seconds to departure, run, serious-love train
夕焼けも照れるわ ギラギラ
Even the sunset gets shy, glaring
じんわり汗も滴るいい女だけど
I'm a good woman with sweat slowly dripping, but...
はぁ、神様、船長はセンシティブだと...
Oh, God, they say the captain is too sensitive...
...BANされちゃうのですね～！はにゃ～ん！
...and will get banned! Hanyann!
100万人記念でもセンシティブな表現を含むため
BANされちゃうのですね～！はにゃん
Even for the 1 million anniversary, it contains sensitive
expressions so I'll get banned! Hanyan
奪われたら 取り戻せ
If it's stolen, take it back
それが宝鐘海賊団
That's the Houshou Pirates
君たちとならたどり着ける
With you all, we can reach it
伝説のエルドラド
The legendary Eldorado
ヨーソロー 楽しけりゃ
Yosoro! If it's fun
歌いYo-ho Yo-ho 足りない
Sing Yo-ho, Yo-ho, it's not enough
あぁ、この景色
Ah, this scenery
大切な仲間よ
My precious comrades
宴だ宴 騒げや騒げ
It's a banquet, a banquet! Make some noise!
踊るアホイに見るアホイ！
Dancing Ahoy, watching Ahoy!
ホイホイ！
Hoi-hoi!
同じアホなら踊らなきゃ損損
If we're all fools, we might as well dance
盃を奪った手にいきますよ それ！
With the hand that grabbed the sake cup, here we go! Sore!
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
宝鐘マリン！
Houshou Marine!
世界で一番？ かわいいよー！
Number one in the world? You're cute!
メスガキメスガキ！
Mesugaki, mesugaki!
エロガキエロガキ！
Erogaki, erogaki!
ボンッキュッボーン！
Hourglass body!
お嬢ちゃんパンツ何色？ パンツ履いてませーん！
Little girl, what color are your panties? I'm not wearing any!
お宝お宝！
Treasure, treasure!
不味い不味い！
Bad, bad!
撫で回すぞー！
I'm gonna pet you all over!
船長のー！ ちょっといいとこ見てみたい！
Captain's! I want to see a good part!
あはーん、あはーん (もっともっと)
Ahann, ahann (more, more)
うふーん、うふーん (もっともっと)
Uhunn, uhunn (more, more)
セクシービーム！ (もっともっと)
Sexy Beam! (more, more)
マッスルマッスル！
Muscle, muscle!
いや～んまいっちんぐ！
Oh my, how embarrassing!
マッスルマッスル！
Muscle, muscle!
どっちゅーの！
Look at this!
まったまったまったまった！
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
サイリスサイリス！
Cy-lith, cy-lith!
まったまったまったまった！
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
萌え萌えキュン！
Moe moe kyun!
まったまったまったまった！
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
出会って５秒で即・出・航！
Setting sail 5 seconds after meeting!
Ahoy!
あ～もう！船長は君たちをそんな子に育てた覚えはありません！
Ah, geez! I don't remember raising you guys to be like that!
本当に！ねるぞ！
Seriously! Let's go to sleep!
立てば痴女、座れば昭和、歩く姿はセンシティブ。
Standing, a pervert; sitting, Showa-era; walking, she's sensitive.
夢を見ようわ　この船で　後悔なんて　させない
Let's dream together on this ship, I won't let you regret it
君たちのおかげで私は　船長になれるから
Because of you all, I can be the Captain
魅惑の船長キャノン　撃てーーー！
Charming Captain Cannon, fire!
ブィーーーーン！
Vroooooom!
声を上げて　さあ出航だ　我ら宝鐘海賊団
Raise your voice, it's time to set sail, we are the Houshou Pirates
コンパス片手に旗を掲げ　この海をジャックしちゃおー！
With compass in hand, raising the flag, let's jack this sea!
良そうついておいで　共にヨーホー　ヨーホー叫ぼう
Follow along nicely, let's shout 'Yo-ho, Yo-ho' together
ああ　最高の最高の日々
Ah, the best, the absolute best of days
ようこそ　我が船へ
Welcome to my ship
宝鐘の海賊団！
The Houshou Pirates!
それでは行きますよ！出航ーーー！
Here we go! Set sail!
ヨーソロー！
Yosoro!
宝鐘マリン100万人記念グッズが出ますよ！
Houshou Marine 1 million subscriber commemorative goods are coming out!
こういうのが欲しかったんでしょう？もう、どすけべ！
You wanted something like this, didn't you? You big pervert!
なんといっても目玉はこちら、あかさあい先生描き下ろし抱き枕カバーです！
The highlight is definitely this: a dakimakura cover illustrated by Akasa Ai-sensei!
君たちはどうせ汚すだろうから予備も買っておいたほうがいいんじゃないですか？
You'll probably get it dirty anyway, so shouldn't you buy a spare?
表面からしてすでにドエッチにもかかわらず、裏面はさらに上をいくドエッチさで、
Even the front side is already super lewd, but the back side is even more so,
とてもじゃないけどYouTubeでは出せません！
to the point where I absolutely cannot show it on YouTube!
ぜひ、概要欄のBOOTHからイラストをご確認ください！
Please check the illustration from the BOOTH link in the description!
そして海賊といえば、やはりみんな頭に巻き散らかしているバンダナ！
And when you think of pirates, you think of bandanas everyone wraps around their heads!
こちらはsaku39さんにデザインしていただきました。
This one was designed by saku39-san.
頭に巻いてもよし、弁当を包んでもよし、何にでも使えるバンダナです。
You can wrap it around your head, or use it to wrap your lunch; it's very versatile.
おしゃれっぽい柄なので、オタクなのがバレない！
It's a stylish pattern, so people won't realize you're an otaku!
バンダナを巻いている時点でオタクと言われたらそれまでですがね。
Though if you're called an otaku just for wearing a bandana, then that's that.
そういえば先日販売開始したノエルの100万人記念グッズも、
By the way, Noel's 1 million subscriber goods that went on sale recently...
3期生みんな写っていててえてえ感じです。
include all the 3rd gen members and they're so wholesome.
3期生推しならこちらも手に入れておきたいのでは？要チェックですよ！
If you're a 3rd gen fan, you'll want to get this too, right? Check it out!
この夏、ホロライブも宝鐘マリンもまだまだイベントやお知らせが待っています。
This summer, Hololive and Houshou Marine still have many events and news waiting.
どうか追いかけてください。
Please keep following us.
君たちに感謝を込めて、出航ーーー！
With gratitude to you all, set sail!
本放送は終了いたしました。ご視聴いただきありがとうございました。
This broadcast has ended. Thank you for watching.